{
    "id": "aa1ca8d9ab3548e78a06404c49409d74",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I waited for him …………………… 10 o’clock and then I went home.",
            "description": "Until and till are interchangeable. Until is more common in a formal style.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec055fe17a2c4350b3b0d0fe3d68006c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked for him everywhere …………………….. I couldn’t find him anywhere.",
            "description": "We use but to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "hence",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8cc8f68a0fb74b73bba56274e6796eb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will buy …………………….. you lower the price.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "44ffa5a3fc6d45f7b77ad3227670862e"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I did not enjoy the program, I sat through it.",
            "description": "Though and although mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e3073e16ce6d49888c80cd356322f075"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. comes to the door, tell them I am out.",
            "description": "Whoever is used to mean ‘it doesn’t matter who….’",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whoever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e3b565b948c43c8934ca233c63b2e47"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you say, I will not believe you.",
            "description": "Whatever is used to mean ‘it doesn’t matter what…’",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07689afa29aa4daab982289a579af8b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… I go to Mumbai, I try to see my cousins.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eaf5059b8f034af5bc9d839609653704"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… you want is fine with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "274d2badd6864b0da943d7fd96e4b065"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should be ready ………………………… the time I come back.",
            "description": "The correct expression is by the time.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00583e650f6449468fa214ba446ebc52"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must finish it ……………………….. you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5bfc363304a44f1c89dec1ee80f11307"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you repair my camera if I leave it …………………… Monday?",
            "description": "We use until to talk about a situation that will continue up to a certain moment.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "by",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8cfa6a8dca4f4fdb9783a6f2402171bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can finish the work ……………………… Monday.",
            "description": "By is used to say that an action will happen before a future moment.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "until",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8cf17cb33321436fa9b9040adc834d74"
        }
    ]
}